Kobato. 24 TL
"The Day That Comes Tomorrow…"
19 eyecatch}
Fukida Lawyer Office
58}
The confetti…
...is being accepted.
Kobato-san’s wish has changed.
But the contract cannot be changed.
She’ll go to the place she wished for.
Isn’t this more like a curse?
What’s going on?
I have to go to the place I belong.
Goodbye.
Wait…!
Are you all right?
Sorry.
Mama told us to clean out the mattress.
Mattress?
Why was there a mattress in an empty room?
Oh.
Fujimoto-san carried it for us!
Kiyokazu-kun, is your arm all right?
Yes.
It’s been a full month, after all.
I see. Thanks.
Mama, what’s that?
Oh, I was thinking of finding a new tenant.
That room’s been empty even before Kiyokazu-kun came,
so it must be pretty lonely without anyone.
I see.
Chitose-san, I’ll ventilate the room from time to time,
so could you leave it unoccupied for a while?
Why?
Huh?
Sorry... for saying something weird.
Kiyokazu, it’s been a while.
Is it true that you didn’t go to the professor’s seminar?
Yeah.
Weren’t you trying to become a lawyer?
I heard you haven’t even been taking notes lately.
What’s gotten into you?
Nothing.
Something’s off about you. It's as if you’ve lost your drive or something.
Not really.
Well…
You did lose something pretty important.
It’s been three months now, eh…
It's too bad about that preschool.
Oh… that isn’t bothering me that much.
It’s just…
Just…?
No…
It’s nothing.
Thank you.
Wow!
The kids were all worried about Yomogi Preschool.
We all came to see it!
Fujimoto-kun, I’m thinking of re-establishing Yomogi Preschool.
Okiura said that he’d do all he could to help this time.
That’s good to hear.
Thank you.
Fujimoto-kun, you hang in there too.
What?
I heard you were moping around at your school.
Doumoto, that bastard…
Once we’re ready, let’s go
on a field trip together again.
Yeah, with everyone…
Everyone…?
Yes, a field trip with everyone.
Oh, a field trip!
That’s right.
Hey, where should we go?
I want to go, too!
That’s right, let’s all go.
Right, Fujimoto-kun?
Y-Yeah.
Yay, everyone together!
Fujimoto-san!
What a bully.
Sorry!
I’ll work hard!
What the heck is this?
What’s going on?!
Why?
How come no one remembers her?
Um…!
Good morning.
Looks like you’re not here to deliver the paper today.
Yes, I remember her.
No one else remembers her.
So why do you…?
Is that what you wanted to ask about?
Is there anything else?
Please tell me.
When she disappeared, she said “I have to go to the place I belong,” right?
What does that mean?
If you truly want to know,
please, don’t be shocked about what you’re about to hear.
Is that all right?
Yeah.
Long ago, she lost her life due to another unfortunate incident in the human world.
Lost her life?
Kobato-san’s wish was…
To cross over time and be reborn so that she could be with the one she loves.
That was Kobato-san’s wish.
And in order to grant that wish,
she accepted a trial and was
allowed to come to this world.
Within those four seasons,
while having a transient soul…
Then… she’s already there?
I don’t know.
Shuichiro-san and I also bid many farewells
during these long months and years.
Shuichiro, that doctor?
Yes.
But every time Shuichiro-san is reborn…
Yes, every time he is reborn,
our hearts pull towards each other and we reunite.
Even if he’s lost the memories of his previous life…
He has the same soul, so…
As long as his soul continues to exist, we’ll always continue on.
Surely…
If the construction machinery was
seized, we wouldn’t know what to do.
It’s all thanks to you, Fukida-sensei.
That’s great news.
Please do your best from now on.
Thank you for everything.
Oh, Fujimoto-kun.
Yes?
You don’t have to worry about the rest,
so read the documents on the desk for me.
It’s a bit far away, so I’ve got a request for you.
Yes, sir.
It’s about an inheritance.
Sensei, who is this?
Oh, Yamauchi, it’s your first time meeting him, right?
This is his fourth year in this office.
Hello, this is Fukida’s office.
He’s still young, but he really has it together.
Fujimoto-kun, it’s secretary
Hattori from the courthouse.
My, if only my son was like that too.
Okay.
The client passed away the other day.
The son and his wife also passed away,
so two years ago, they wrote a will to
give their inheritance to the grandchild.
But according to the real estate papers, they’re an old lineage,
and the boundaries of the land are unclear as well.
I see.
I’ll go investigate the location tomorrow.
…saku hana
The flowers that bloom in the spring
natsu hirogaru sora yo
The spacious summer skies
kokoro no…
Engraves and glistens
You’re from the lawyer’s office?
Nice to meet you.
Same here…
Even if he’s lost the memories of his previous life…
Hey!
Stop! Please!
Fujimoto-san…
...is my important person.
Up until now…
And from now on…
Always…
Piano…
You’re good at playing the piano.
Sorry for playing without asking.
I know that song as well for some reason.
Isn’t that odd?
I see…
It’s a song someone important to me sang long ago…
I’ve been looking for that person since then.
I see.
I hope you find that person.
Yes…
Well then, is it all right if I
inspect the inside of the house?
Oh, yes!
That’s it.
All that’s left is to process the inheritance back at the office.
Okay. Thank you!
And this… I need to give it back to you.
Yes?
Confetti?
Will you sing that song one last time?
Yes!
haruni saku hana
The flowers that bloom in the spring
natsu hirogaru sora yo
The spacious summer skies
kokoro no naka ni
Engraves and glistens
kizamarete kirameku
Inside my heart
asa ni furu ame
Even in the rain that falls in the morning
mado wo tozasu hi ni mo
And the day that I shut my window
mune ni afureru
My heart is overflowing
hikari wa kumo no…
Because the light is shining above the clouds
Um, are you all right?
That’s right…
The place I wanted to go…
To be beside my most important person…
If we were to meet again, I told
myself to say it with a smile this time…
I’m… so hopeless.
Kobato?
I’m back!
You made me wait so many years.
You really overslept.
Fujimoto-san!
yorokobi kanashimi
Happiness and sorrow
subete idaite aruiteru
I embrace them all and continue to walk
watashi no te to kimi no te wo
Take my hand along with your hand
tsuyoku tsunagu mono
And make a powerful bond
aki wa mizube ni
Autumn lies hidden
fuyu kozue ni hisomu
in the treetops at the waterfront
sekai no oku no
In the depths of the earth
kagiri nai yasashisa
lies unlimited kindness
yoru ga kuru tabi
Each time the night comes,
Well, that’s how it is.
Even though that idiot fulfilled his mission,
he decided to watch over
that girl in the human world,
inori wo sasageyou
we’ll offer a prayer
so we’re still here making baumkuchen.
ashita kuru hi wo
We’ll quietly greet
Yeah.
It’s yummy, baumkuchen!
shizuka ni mukaeyou
the next day
Well, well.
I deserve 100 points.
watashi wo michibiku
Please guide me
tooi tooi yobigoe yo
O voice from the great distance
hohoemu youni
It seems like it’s smiling
utau youni
It seems like it’s singing
hibiku kaze no oto
The sound of the echoing breeze
yorokobi kanashimi
Happiness and sorrow
subete idaite aruiteru
I embrace them all and continue to walk
watashi no te to kimi no te wo
Take my hand along with your hand
tsuyoku tsunagu mono
And make a powerful bond